Welcome to the Expense [music] Agent
series. This video is going to be about
feedback. Your feedback is very
important to us. We want to make sure
that we can get the right feedback that
we need and make it as easy as possible
for you to provide that. So,
as we dive in to the product, we've made
it as easy as possible to click
and give not only positive feedback, but
also suggestions
and report any issues that you find.
You may be familiar with communicating
directly to partners when you run into
issues.
You can also get the support information
that you need from this help pane to
share with them.
But also, no matter where you provide
feedback in the product, whether it's
here or from the header, or where I'm
going to show you next, all of that same
support information will be provided to
us so we can follow up on it.
Now, I want to dive into the product
here. If you want to provide some
contextual feedback, something specific
to the expenses that you run into,
something that worked really well, you
can let us know here. Or if something
didn't work well, definitely please let
us know.
What's really important about this
is you'll be able to provide as much
information as you feel comfortable. You
can capture your screenshots here.
And in case the screenshots show
personal information that you don't want
to show, we make it very easy to hide
that
from us as well as be able to highlight
the information that is important to
you.
So, we can use that.
We can save that screenshot and we can
type anything that you think is
important to let us know how to make
this product better for you in the
future.
If you'd like to be contacted, you can
let us know that here. Or if you don't,
And fine. We will still follow
with all of the feedback that you
provide.
And so that's how you can provide
feedback to help us make expense agent a
better experience for you.
Thank you for watching the video.